(function(){const t=document.createElement("link").relList;if(t&&t.supports&&t.supports("modulepreload"))return;for(const o of document.querySelectorAll('link[rel="modulepreload"]'))S(o);new MutationObserver(o=>{for(const r of o)if(r.type==="childList")for(const u of r.addedNodes)u.tagName==="LINK"&&u.rel==="modulepreload"&&S(u)}).observe(document,{childList:!0,subtree:!0});function R(o){const r={};return o.integrity&&(r.integrity=o.integrity),o.referrerpolicy&&(r.referrerPolicy=o.referrerpolicy),o.crossorigin==="use-credentials"?r.credentials="include":o.crossorigin==="anonymous"?r.credentials="omit":r.credentials="same-origin",r}function S(o){if(o.ep)return;o.ep=!0;const r=R(o);fetch(o.href,r)}})();const Y=[{id:1,question:"Which of the following is not a type of music notation?",options:["Standard notation","Tab notation","Morse code notation","Graphics notation"],answer:"Morse code notation",category:"music"},{id:2,question:"What is the most common time signature in classical music?",options:["3/4","4/4","5/4","6/8"],answer:"4/4",category:"music"},{id:3,question:"Which of the following is not a type of instrument in a symphony orchestra?",options:["Violin","Piano","Harp","Theremin"],answer:"Theremin",category:"music"},{id:4,question:"What is the most common key in pop music?",options:["C Major","G Major","D Major","A Major"],answer:"C Major",category:"music"},{id:5,question:"Which of the following is not a type of chord?",options:["Major","Minor","Diminished","Flat"],answer:"Flat",category:"music"},{id:6,question:"Which of the following is not a type of music genre?",options:["Jazz","Blues","Rock","Applesauce"],answer:"Applesauce",category:"music"},{id:7,question:"Which of the following is not a type of music theory?",options:["Harmony","Counterpoint","Form","Cooking"],answer:"Cooking",category:"music"},{id:8,question:"What is the most common tempo marking in classical music?",options:["Allegro","Andante","Adagio","Moderato"],answer:"Allegro",category:"music"},{id:9,question:"Which of the following is not a type of musical form?",options:["Sonata","Symphony","Concerto","Spaghetti"],answer:"Spaghetti",category:"music"},{id:10,question:"Which of the following is not a type of music notation software?",options:["Sibelius","Finale","MuseScore","Microsoft Word"],answer:"Microsoft Word",category:"music"}],K=[{id:11,question:"Which artist is known for coining the term 'Surrealism'?",options:["Pablo  Picasso","Salvador Dali","Vincent van Gogh","Henri Matisse"],answer:"Salvador Dali",category:"modern-art"},{id:12,question:"Which movement is associated with the use of abstract forms and shapes in art?",options:["Impressionism","Expressionism"," Futurism","Cubism"],answer:"Cubism",category:"modern-art"},{id:13,question:"Which artist is known for painting the work 'The Persistence of Memory'?",options:["Pablo Picasso","Salvador Dali","Vincent van Gogh"," Henri Matisse"],answer:"Salvador Dali",category:"modern-art"},{id:14,question:"Which artist is known for creating the painting 'The Scream'?",options:[" Vincent van Gogh"," Salvador Dali","Edvard Munch","Claude Monet"],answer:"Edvard Munch",category:"modern-art"},{id:15,question:"What movement was associated with the use of bold, bright colors and thick brushstrokes?",options:["Impressionism "," Expressionism"," Fauvism"," Cubism"],answer:"Fauvism",category:"modern-art"},{id:16,question:"What movement was associated with the use of bright colors, simplified forms, and a focus on movement and speed",options:[" Impressionism","Futurism","Surrealism","Abstract Expressionism"],answer:"Futurism",category:"modern-art"},{id:17,question:"Which artist is known for creating the painting 'Water Lilies'?",options:[" Claude Monet","Paul Cezanne","Paul Gauguin","Paul Klee"],answer:"Claude Monet",category:"modern-art"},{id:18,question:"Which artist is known for creating the painting 'Les Demoiselles d'Avignon'?",options:["Henri Matisse ","Vincent van Gogh ","Salvador Dali ","Pablo Picasso "],answer:"Pablo Picasso",category:"modern-art"},{id:19,question:"Which artist is known for creating the painting 'Guernica'?",options:["Claude Mone","Paul Cezanne"," Pablo Picasso","Vincent van Gogh"],answer:"Pablo Picasso",category:"modern-art"},{id:20,question:"Which artist is known for creating the sculpture 'The Thinker'?",options:["Auguste Rodin","Alexander Calder","Jean Arp","Henry Moore"],answer:"Auguste Rodin",category:"modern-art"}],U=[{id:21,question:"What is the correct syntax for an if statement in Python?",options:["if (condition):","if condition","if: condition","if condition:"],answer:"if condition:",category:"coding"},{id:22,question:"Which of the following is not a data type in JavaScript?",options:["String","Number","Boolean","ArrayList"],answer:"ArrayList",category:"coding"},{id:23,question:"Which of the following is used to declare a variable in Java?",options:["var","let","const","int"],answer:"int",category:"coding"},{id:24,question:"What is the correct syntax for a for loop in C#?",options:["for i = 0 to 10","for (i = 0; i <= 10; i++)","for (int i = 0; i <= 10)","for i in range(0, 10)"],answer:"for (i = 0; i <= 10; i++)",category:"coding"},{id:25,question:"Which of the following is not a looping structure in PHP?",options:["while","for","do-while","foreach"],answer:"foreach",category:"coding"},{id:26,question:"Which of the following is not a valid operator in C++?",options:["+","-","*","$"],answer:"$",category:"coding"},{id:27,question:"In which programming language is 'print' used for displaying output?",options:["Python","JavaScript","Java"," C++ "],answer:"Python",category:"coding"},{id:28,question:"What is the correct syntax for a function in Ruby?",options:["function name()","def name","function name","def name()"],answer:"def name()",category:"coding"},{id:29,question:"Which of the following is not a type of variable in Swift?",options:["Int","String","Double","Object"],answer:"Object",category:"coding"},{id:30,question:"In which programming language is '#' used for commenting?",options:["Python","JavaScript","Java","C++"],answer:"C++",category:"coding"}],l={music:Y,modernArt:K,coding:U};localStorage.setItem("myJson",JSON.stringify(l));const X=localStorage.getItem("myJson");JSON.parse(X);localStorage.setItem("myJson",JSON.stringify(l));const Z=localStorage.getItem("myJson"),a=JSON.parse(Z),_=document.querySelector(".music, .coding, .modernArt"),ee=document.querySelector(".ques"),m=document.querySelectorAll(".ans"),te=document.querySelector(".back"),w=document.querySelector(".next"),q=document.querySelector("#ansA"),b=document.querySelector("#ansB"),v=document.querySelector("#ansC"),$=document.querySelector("#ansD");let n=0,M=0,k="";localStorage.getItem("attempted");f();function f(){oe();const e=a.music[n];if(ee.innerHTML=`${n+1}: `+e.question,A.innerText=e.options[0],B.innerText=e.options[1],C.innerText=e.options[2],D.innerText=e.options[3],k=JSON.parse(localStorage.getItem("attempted")))for(let t=0;t<4;t++)if(k.includes(a.music[n].options[t])){q.disabled=!0,b.disabled=!0,v.disabled=!0,$.disabled=!0,m[t].checked=!0;return}else q.disabled=!1,b.disabled=!1,v.disabled=!1,$.disabled=!1}w.addEventListener("click",()=>{const e=ne();e!=0&&(e===a.music[n].answer&&M++,n++,n+1===10&&(w.innerHTML="Submit Quiz"),n<a.music.length?f():_.innerHTML=`<h2>You answered ${M}/${a.music.length} questions correctly</h2> `)});let J=[];function oe(){m.forEach(e=>e.checked=!1)}function ne(){let e;return m.forEach(t=>{if(t.checked)t.id==="ansA"&&(e=a.music[n].options[0]),t.id==="ansB"&&(e=a.music[n].options[1]),t.id==="ansC"&&(e=a.music[n].options[2]),t.id==="ansD"&&(e=a.music[n].options[3]),J.push(e);else return 0;localStorage.setItem("attempted",JSON.stringify(J))}),e}te.addEventListener("click",()=>{n>0&&(n--,f())});window.onbeforeunload=function(e){localStorage.clear("attempted")};localStorage.setItem("myJson",JSON.stringify(l));const ie=localStorage.getItem("myJson"),c=JSON.parse(ie),se=document.querySelector(".music, .coding, .modernArt"),re=document.querySelector(".ques"),g=document.querySelectorAll(".ans");document.querySelector("#A");document.querySelector("#B");document.querySelector("#C");document.querySelector("#D");const ae=document.querySelector(".back"),W=document.querySelector(".next"),T=document.querySelector("#ansA"),P=document.querySelector("#ansB"),x=document.querySelector("#ansC"),L=document.querySelector("#ansD");let i=0,I="",O=0;h();function h(){ce();const e=c.modernArt[i];if(re.innerHTML=`${i+1}: `+e.question,A.innerText=e.options[0],B.innerText=e.options[1],C.innerText=e.options[2],D.innerText=e.options[3],I=JSON.parse(localStorage.getItem("attempted")))for(let t=0;t<4;t++)if(I.includes(c.modernArt[i].options[t])){T.disabled=!0,P.disabled=!0,x.disabled=!0,L.disabled=!0,g[t].checked=!0;return}else T.disabled=!1,P.disabled=!1,x.disabled=!1,L.disabled=!1}function ce(){g.forEach(e=>e.checked=!1)}let E=[];function de(){let e;return g.forEach(t=>{if(t.checked)t.id==="ansA"&&(e=c.modernArt[i].options[0]),t.id==="ansB"&&(e=c.modernArt[i].options[1]),t.id==="ansC"&&(e=c.modernArt[i].options[2]),t.id==="ansD"&&(e=c.modernArt[i].options[3]),E.push(e);else return 0;localStorage.setItem("attempted",JSON.stringify(E))}),e}W.addEventListener("click",()=>{const e=de();e!=0&&(e===c.modernArt[i].answer&&O++,i++,i+1===10&&(W.innerHTML="Submit Quiz"),i<c.modernArt.length?h():se.innerHTML=`
         <h2>You answered ${O}/${c.modernArt.length} questions correctly</h2>
         `)});ae.addEventListener("click",()=>{i>0&&(i--,h())});window.onbeforeunload=function(e){localStorage.clear()};localStorage.setItem("myJson",JSON.stringify(l));const le=localStorage.getItem("myJson"),d=JSON.parse(le),ue=document.querySelector(".music, .coding, .modernArt"),me=document.querySelector(".ques"),p=document.querySelectorAll(".ans");document.querySelector("#A");document.querySelector("#B");document.querySelector("#C");document.querySelector("#D");const fe=document.querySelector(".back"),N=document.querySelector(".next"),z=document.querySelector("#ansA"),H=document.querySelector("#ansB"),Q=document.querySelector("#ansC"),F=document.querySelector("#ansD");let s=0,G="",j=0;y();function y(){ge();const e=d.coding[s];if(me.innerHTML=`${s+1}: `+e.question,A.innerText=e.options[0],B.innerText=e.options[1],C.innerText=e.options[2],D.innerText=e.options[3],G=JSON.parse(localStorage.getItem("attempted")))for(let t=0;t<4;t++)if(G.includes(d.coding[s].options[t])){z.disabled=!0,H.disabled=!0,Q.disabled=!0,F.disabled=!0,p[t].checked=!0;return}else z.disabled=!1,H.disabled=!1,Q.disabled=!1,F.disabled=!1}function ge(){p.forEach(e=>e.checked=!1)}let V=[];function he(){let e;return p.forEach(t=>{if(t.checked)t.id==="ansA"&&(e=d.coding[s].options[0]),t.id==="ansB"&&(e=d.coding[s].options[1]),t.id==="ansC"&&(e=d.coding[s].options[2]),t.id==="ansD"&&(e=d.coding[s].options[3]),V.push(e);else return 0;localStorage.setItem("attempted",JSON.stringify(V))}),e}N.addEventListener("click",()=>{const e=he();e!=0&&(e===d.coding[s].answer&&j++,s++,s+1===10&&(N.innerHTML="Submit Quiz"),s<d.coding.length?y():ue.innerHTML=`
         <h2>You answered ${j}/${d.coding.length} questions correctly</h2>
        
         `)});fe.addEventListener("click",()=>{s>0&&(s--,y())});window.onbeforeunload=function(e){localStorage.clear()};
